

Jeoffrey Duke

Web-Developer

Contacts

01 Joe Duke Crescent jeoffreyduke@gmail.com +2349071400408 jeoffreyduke.web.app github.com/jeoffreyduke

Skills

HTML5

CSS3

TypeScript

Solidity

Web3 js

React is

Next js

MySQL

MongoDB

Redux

Express js

React-Native

Git

Profile

I am a young, creative and enthusiastic web developer with over 2 years of experience building various Web Applications; be it as personal projects or professional work. i am well-versed with technologies such as HTML, CSS, Vanilla JS, Typescript, Solidity, Web3 JS, React JS, React Native, Express JS, Redux, gsap, THREE JS, MySQL, MongoDB, Mongoose etc. I currently work remotely as an Intern for a company in the UK.

Education

University of Calabar 2019 – 2023

Bachelor of Science in Environmental Science

Christian Science College 2011 – 2017

Senior School Certifcate

Auntie Margaret International School 2005 – 2011

First School Living Certificate

Employment

Full-Stack Web Developer at SockTech 2020 – 2021

Worked as a Full-Stack Web Developer for SockTech(a start up company at the time) for over two years.

Part-time Freelancer on Upwork 2020 – 2022

Developed numerous websites of all types and guaranteed that they exceeded the expectations of our clients.

Internships

Industrial Trainee at Nearkeen Technologies 2020 – 2021

This was where i gained most of my valuable professional skills in terms of working with other people

Industrial Trainee at Reboost, UK 2022 – present

I started working here on October 2022, and I have worked predominantly with React.is; building tons of website templates.